Doramon part 2
how wonderful this is
only if it could come true
this dream, that dream,
so many of them
all of them can come true
incredible pocket
make your dreams come true
I really want to fly in the sky
no problem
bamboo dragonfly
ononon, my favorite
doramon
asia_cartoon@hotmail.com
run, machine horse
see, I can step up this high
no big deal, I can use only one leg
cool
I can't believe you
have so much fun on this
it won't change your value
if you can do it or not
let's have a stepping horse race tor-tomorrow
what do you say
sounds fun, let's do it
lam not going to lose
I will be number 1 for sure
because I only use one leg
such a boring thing
hey, nobita, will you join us
forget about him, he is not able to do it
it's a pressure to ask him to join us
really, did I say something cruel
damn
what, you told them
you want to join the contest
yes, I cant stand the way saying me
since I am a real man, I can't back up
you can't back up
so, please, doramon, help me out
since you are begging me like this
you have guts
you don't know how to do it
but still you want to join the contest
your spirit is very good
ok, dad will make you a bamboo horse
when I was little
,we didn't have toys to play with
we had to make our own toys
see, done
90909090
but still I don't know how to do it, right
who told you to promise them
doramon, help me out
you always do this to me,
it's weird that nobita promised to join
the contest so bravely
so he will definitely ask doramon
to use future machine to help him out
it's always like this and he will win
lam not going to let him win this time
please help me out
it's not in to play
with bamboo horse in 22 century
it's ok it's not in just get me your stuff
it's easy for you to say
, but , there is a machine bamboo horse
machine bamboo horse
as long as it's a bamboo horse, show me
but it's kind of
I can't make myself
embarrassed in front of sitzuka
ok,ok, I take it out
show me
it's not my responsibility
if something is going wrong
ok, hang on
what's this, an animal
the mix of horse and bamboo
machine bamboo horse
yike, stay away from me
it's the high tech of 22 century
you can ride it in high speed
an you won't fall off
that cool, let me try
wow, it's true
ouch
are you ok, nobita
I was shocked, what's going on
it must be angry
I know, because of your dirty feet
machine bamboo horse is very picky
how annoying
feed it some carrots
will it eat
see, it worke, treat it nice
and ride it at the same time
it's difficult
good
wow new toy
cool, I will get number 1 tomorrow
sorry
cool
awesome
damn, nobita is using that thing
there is no chance for us to win
bummer, how can you give up so easily
it's so fun
let it rest till tomorrow
what, you made it a bamboo horse
, so how do I dry the clothe
sorry, let me find some substitution,
there you go, this is just right
what a weird stick
no, there is nothing wrong with it
HO
ouch
follow me home, I will treat you nice
what, machine bamboo horse ran away
that's neither a bar-bamboo horse
nor a stick
yes, don't keep a dangerous thing at home
I know
tomorrow, people will laugh at me
no, it's better in this way
why
if you really want to ride on it
Just do it like a man
nobita, aren't you a real man
first, you have to practice riding
on it and walk
whoever can do this
shut up
ok,I know, I will do it
let me try higher
no, I can't walk like this
the height is no big deal, just go
right, left, right, left, right, left
don't be afraid to fall down and get hurt
90909090
doramon is very strict
ready to run, go
yes, that's the way
lam not going to lose
look ahead, look ahead, look
what the hell, this simple task
what couldn't”: I do this before
see, I am wounded everywhere
machine bamboo horse
it's giant
why are you bringing
this kind of stuff with you?
I don't know why it's like that
ouch, it hurts
it's mad because the house is dirty
it's not my business
yes, I do
that, I know I am bold
but please would you be my friend
that girl was so shy
after she heard me say that
hey, what's next, then she said what, hey
nothing
don't hold back, tell me, you stingy
you are annoying, not your business
would you be my friend
she left
and didn't even look back
that girl lived at
her friend's place for 3 days
so you wanted to be her friend
watch this, choopit's arrow
what's that
doramon, what's that toy arrow for
can't you tell
let's use this arrow
it's cruel
it's ok, it doesn't hurt if you are shot
the one who is shot
will like the one who shoots
and if you pull out the arrow
everything will be back to normal
cool
like I did just now
just shoot at the person you like
don't know if I can make it or not
it's her, great opportunity
hurry, shoot her
let's make it happen
FUN
wait, no, wow
lam sure she lives here
it will be great if I can see her
ok, let's sneak in to see if she is inside
who are you
it's rude to peek on someone's house
doramon, is there another way to do it
it's not helpful like
this even we have this
ok, use white cloth to get her out
how convenient
he wanted to peek on you just now
what a lousy guy
really
you always get punished because you
are late and don't hand out the homework
and there is a weird robot
next to him named doramon
it's funny, naramon
not nonamon, but doramon
who is talking
ah, my book
don't run
wait
I got found out
shoot
cor-me over here, let's play
HO
don't be shy, help
nobita, just pull out the arrow
give me a break
hey, you horny robot touched my ass
help
wait up
only one arrow left
you have to use it right
ms. Tun
weird, where did I shoot
uncle, did you see
an arrow coming this way
great face, let me see you closer
don't talk about my face, I know it's ugly
it's not
doramon, cheer up
what a great face
tall nose, confident mouth, shinny eyes
really
I have never been told like that before
please, say it again
is my face really that charmy
say it again
like a hippo
damn
give it UP
yes, give it up
drop it
we made it
arrange the next date, it's cool
it's great, nobita
I am home,
nobita, you are home
I have been waiting for long
tun
ah, the arrow is still there
doramon, pull it out for me
wait for me, nobita
damn, I can't help you out anymore
asia_cartoons@sinaman.com
traffice tools combination
cook, I want to be like him too
to beat up those bad guys
and he is fast
hey, you have gone too far
can't believe you did this do me
what's that
traffice tools combination
just put it on you and
you will become any kind of vehicle
for example, like this
you can be like a tank going wherever
cool, this is way too cool
and if you put this on you will be
like a submarine diving in the water
cool, let me play with it
but I just bought it
it's not for a kid
it won't cost you anything to lend me this
no way
just for a while
HO
hey, there is the dumpling vender
he is leaving
dumpling
hehe, I got it
cool, it's like a robot
put this on and then
you can beat up those bad guys
who want to rule the world and monsters
ok, watch this
it's ok not to be a monster
a robot is fine too
anyway, just let me know if you need me
justice man
superman nobita will fly to you
you lier, there was no dumpling vender
you fooled me and stole my tool, right
lam going to put it away
no, I have promised them
please, lend it to me
HO
not just for fun
I don”: trust you
lam serious, for justice
HO
he said go to him if I need help
what the hell, how cocky he is
the trouble is always caused by him
anyway, he will borrow something
from doramon for sure
let him show us what's he got
can't you just trust me
ok, we are not friends anymore
whatever
lam joking, for justice
I want to borrow it from you, please
nobita, bad news
sitzuka said something urgent
you have got to go now
see, for rescuing sitzuka
please lend it to me
wow, great
it's fast, wait for me, lam on my way
sorry for waiting
who did this to you
it's that wild cat
it took away my favorite doll
eh, for catching a wild cat
it's running away, go get it
hurry, it's running away, I know
what the hell
I can't believe I the superman nobita
is catching this wild cat, it sucks
damn, don't go
thanks, nobita, you really are a
superman nobita, thanks
I made it
nobita the superman
I have something to ask you for a favor
ok, shoot
my mom forgot this and left the house
please send this to her for me
please
why am I doing these boring things
hey, don't walk over there on my window
it's another rude person walking
on someone's window
eh, window
thanks for bringing this to me
catching a wild cat, delivering
what I want is fighting with a moster
but it doesn't really exist
no good
nobita, follow me, there is a monster
a monster
where, where is it
lam on my way, go go, hurry
wow, a monster
here comes nobita the superman
will there be a monster in here
are you scared, jump down
bummer, lam here for the monster
there is no way for me to be scared
no, where is the monster
umm, shopping bag
it's shell
someone dropped it
on the way to go shopping
and this is all I have found
there is no monster in the ditch
I only found this
great, I thought you couldn't find it
I dropped it on my way
to go shopping for my mom
so you lied telling me
there was a monster, you
I didn't, I did buy 10 oysters
do you call it a monster
(10 oysters sound the same as a monster)
there are 10 oysters, so it's called
lam not lying, then, bye
pretty mai
if I really have to describe you
as a flower will be a carnation
proud like a queen
shinny like a star
you are so beautiful
it's true
when I look at her my eyes
are wide open, and my legs are shivering
my heart is pumping like a drum
and I can't even eat
the favorite food I like, dumpling
why don't you just go
tell her how much you like her
I am shy
ok, I will tell her for you
thanks, nobita
you always help me out
lam doing this for
what you have done for me
over there
where, there
where is there, doramon
beneath nobita's feet
doramon, are you saying this
yes, lam so shy
what the hell, it's just a toy cat
can't it be a toy cat
I am a robot cat
what's so wrong to like a toy cat
you are right
but the toy cat doesn't suit you well
whatever, I am leaving, wait
you are so shy
ok, I am a man too
just go to her and tell her
my name is doramon
I like you very much, do you like me
she said, yes, great
great
would you be my friend
great she said yes
ok, let's have a date, hey you
what do you think about me
for example, I am a sweet person
or do I make you feel secure
tell me, don't be shy ok
hey, what are you doing don't you
feel shame to steal a child's toy
we are in love
please don't break us apart
please let mei marry me
I will make her happy
so please let her marry me
dear
what is he talking about
what, doramon is at your house
don”: worry, I will bring him back
no, I am not going back
don't be a baby, let's go home
no, go home
the stick will be broken down, stop it
I said, stop it
there is a dog grabbing
away my toy, what, mai was
I can't let this happen, damn, mai
hey, give mai back
mai, ouch, it hurts
doramon
lam going to protect her no matter what
Thai
doramon, you did a good job, mai mai
do you still want the toy
ok, you can have it
did you hear that, doramon, it's great
Thai
this is the dumpling, have some
eh, you don't like sweet stuff
what, you want some fish, ok
how can a toy eat fish, it's so funny
she just can eat fish
she is really eating
what's going on
I plugged her
an automatic feeding installation
by the way, let me put on all
kinds of installations
to make her a totally robat cat
walk automatically
climb trees automatically
tickle automatically, speak automatically
come on, mai, let me make you free
done
cool
where am I , who are you
this is my house, lam nobita
lam doramon, your groom
I hate you saying you are my groom
why do you hate me being your groom
in fact
in fact what
I am a male
lam out to play
doramon, cheer up
don't cry, doramon
there are not happy things every day
no, I don't care
doramon, it's useless to cry
asia_cartoon@hotmail.com
toy troop
where are you hiding, nobita
get out of there
hiding is not a proud behavior
get your ass out of there
ok, nobita, you are not coming out huh
you think you are save hiding there huh
or are you gone, in your dream
I will find you
and make you my karate target
punch you 30 times
then I will be feeling good
he is annoying, he always likes to get mad
ok, here it is,
hey, it's nobita
come fetch me, I can't go home alone
urn, giant
he.. It's not the first time tho
lam busy, I can't help you out now
let me send a toy to fetch you
it's been really serious situation
don't be so cold, come fetch me
don't worry
I will send you a powerful company
no matter who the enemy is
he can easily beat him up
order, no matter when, protect nobita well
lam counting on you
let me finish my puzzle
doramon, doramon
it's great to see you again
in a while my powerful
company will come to rescue me
don't bluff
I mean it
lam not going to buy you
help
give it up , you , watch this
ha, your powerful company, these toys huh
they do look powerful , right, nobita
watch me
it's impossible
I am save now
I didn't Know you were this strong
for your sake
now I am not afraid of anything
ah, my ball
hey, how are you going to
compensate me, it's my best ball
sorry, I will pay you back
that's not enough, ouch
don't tell those weird things to stink me,
wait, it was our fault,
ready
attack
what a stubburn guy
as long as he thinks you are his enemy
he will beat you up no matter how
help
looks like I have to ask doramon
to take back the order
yes, just climb up and I will be safe
ready, shoot
Shit
damn, it's more annoying
what's wrong, you look so depressed
bummer, moron she is not hitting me
don't get her wrong
eh, where is nobita
he is still playing outside, not home yet
I wanted to ask him to go shopping for me
you do it
sorry, I am busy
you guys
eh
nobita, where have you been, I
stop, you'd better not be mad at me
what are you talking about
mom, it's because
stop, she is my mom, not an enemy
stop, I told you to stop
ready
morn, run
wow, help
wait
damn it, gotta tell doramon
to make them stop
doramon
come on over, bad things happened
hurry, mom
ah, what are you doing, lam almost done
mom, sorry
before doramon wakes up
you'd better hide yourself somewhere
somebody, help
wake up
help
attack
what should I do now
what do you think
from here you can see how big the fish is
you can't see this from anywhere else
my parents bought these after I was born
they wanted me to grow up
like these fish, strong and healthy
an I do believe what they said
I feel bad for those kids
who can”: afford to buy those fish
it's really lonely that you don't have
the fish for children's day
tzo just cried out loud all of a sudden
what's going on
bummer
foo, you are cruel
THOTH
what' s wrong tzo
I want that fish flag
please buy it for me
you promised me last year
sorry, tzo
I don't have money to buy it for you
let's wait until next year, ok
no, no
I want that fish flag.
tzo has no father
his mom raised him alone
and you showed off in front him
shame on you
you hurt such a little kid
you are very thoughtful huh
do the soul refresh thing, you idiot
cruel guy
devil
I know, you are trying to kick me out
why don't you give him your flag
damn, ok
what the hell
everyone sees me as an enemy
damn, even my flag
ok, give it to him now
stop it, what are you doing
don't do it
don't cut the flag
shut up
I am going to give part of it to him
wait for me
I can't put up with this
calm down, everybody
shut up, just split it up
and give half of the flag to tzo
now you are happy huh
why did you do this
let me do it, I have a good idea
why did you borrow this flag
just let me do it
ok, first
um, I got it
what's this
cloud machine
wow, what's this, cool
hey, doramon, what's going on
don't worry, as long as this room is
full of clouds, the flags can float then
after the clouds are done
just use this machine to control
the flag and make it float in the clouds
see, this is the way
does it really float
wow, it is floating
cool, doramon, what's next
you will see
great, later the little fish
will give birth baby fish
really
I need some food for the fish
get some cookies, get a lot
ok
it's getting more interesting
I got it
hurry
nobita, don't eat so many cookies
not for me, for the fish
I see, ok then
sorry for waiting, here you are
right timing you came, see it's giving
birth now, we will have babies soon
wow, so many eggs
this is the egg
wow, it's moving
great
one after the other
how cute
ok, now feed them cookies
eat as much as possible
so you can grow up fast
more, come
feed fish flag with cookies
do you think I am an idiot or what
hey, nobita, get out of your place
doramon, they are growing up
ok, almost done
let's go to tzo's house
I see
it's a great idea
tzo will be happy
wow, fish flags, they are here
great, tzo
our fish flags are the best
they mean children swining around with fun
old tool competition
this is an old record player
called juke box
these are old too
and alatin pot and a this shield
they are hard to find now
but why are you
collecting those old dirty things
anyway, after having a car
air con, microwave
these old dirty things make you
feel like back to old times, you know
sorry, I am too talkative now
do you have anything like this at home
yes, there are lots of old
things at my home
what are they
UT“
tv set, washing machine
they are pretty old, like 10 years old
and vacuum cleaner
refrigerator, they are old too
ha, those are worthless stuff
you know nothing
damn
I want something old
it's my first time being laughed at
especially it was in front of sitzuka
now I am going to show foo something
please doramon
ok, count on me
let me contact the antique
shop in 22 century
but it's expensive to buy old stuff
just trade our things with them
ok, let's do it
what about this old radio
I think it's OK
hey, antique shot
this is doramon speaking
I want to trade you
an older stuff with 1976 made radio
shoot
got it, let's do it now
wow, what's this, cool
it's the antique mineral radio
this is a radio
now we are forecasting the weather
today in Tokyo area
what do you think
it's rare huh, this is a very old radio
let me hear it
me too
is this the only thing you have
I have something better
what, lam not going to lose you
doramon
doramon, he is not here
let me contact it with this
hello, antique shop
yes, thanks for calling
I want to buy some more old stuff
what's to trade this time
um, whatever, I'll let you deal with it
the older stuff the better
I got it.
I will let you Know as soon as I find it
what will it be
lam really looking forward to it
I see, is this an antique too
this is not rare
exactly
what about this
wow, you look great,
antique shop
I want something more special
good, I got some good stuff
the costume for xxx from 1000 years ago
cool
it's really rare
and it's getting older
it's ape
cool
wow, this is too old to be true
HO more
I have found some old furniture too
now let's trade them one after one
why is that
I thought the washing machine
as a washing board
I must be sick , gotta take some pills
whats going on
lam home, I bought something
lam a princess
must be nobita traing things
by time cell phone, gotta stop him
nobita
achoo, no good
ok, now nobody is here, gotta run home
why are you naked walking
on the street, I have to arrest you
uncle cop, let me go, it's a serious crime
shut up , be quiet
what's going on
nobita
doramon
nobita, how can you trade whatever
sorry
where is the time cell phone
damn, you are so irresponsible
what if someone took it away
I take off early, go get a drink
eh, my home should be here
honey
where is my home
eh, it's my home
yes, thanks for calling
ah, got it
hello, antique shop
please make all the things back
lam afraid I can't do that all thing
are sold and can't buy them back
you are giving me a hard time
do something
there is nothing I can do
if it's new, I can do it now
ok, new stuff is fine, do it now
ms. Coffee
fire
get out of my way, stop it
hey, make everything back to what
they were like, nobody is used to them
hot
asia_cartoons@sinaman.com
making craft is fun
ouch
give it back to me
it looks like a funny round plate
it's a frisbee
didn't you do it
by the way, I left it unfinished at home
I threw it away, I have never used it tho
why
you don't know how anyway
I was trying to make it
wow, dumpling
I know, let me give you the substitute
everything is here
wow, it's big
it's easy to make tho
indeed
let's do it
ok
see, it's easy to be done
seems like you really can ride on it
of course
press the button
see, it's flying
stay out of trouble
it's fun
I have made a frisbee too
sitzuka , where are you doing
this lamp is broken
you have to have it fixed
there is a manual
to tell you how to make a lamp
wait, let me make a new one for you
it's getting boring
it's all nobita's fault
doing something like that
so
it's pretty, thank you
nice
nobita, please
they want to do that too
let me give them another one
don't do anything weird
can't be lost, gotta do something cool
what about this
it takes 40 pages to do it
ok, let's do it
paper gun, paper vest, paper hat
don't run, ban
we are indians
don't run, banban
what a big
what's wrong
help us
we have done something we shouldn't do
do something
what do you expect me to do
you are a cowboy
by the way,use this
bummer, what if you hit me
how can you beat it up with a cork
ah, it ate it up
help us
gogogo, giant, keep it like that
let me rescue you with cannon
I will make a weapon to rescue you
hold on a second
don't be kidding, told me to hang on
FUN
what do I do now, I have to get rid of him
it's all giant's fault
he said that he wanted to make that thing
why me
are you playing hide and seek
shh, the dinosaur will find us
what are you talking about, dinosaur
I see, so it's made of paper
why don't you just burn it
there is a person with round face
there is a person with long face
there is person with square face
there is a person with triangle face
just cry out loud and be made, be moody
you like to cry and you
will become a devil
but, but , smile
everybody is round faced